Abdurrahman Yahaya Ahmad

Frontend Developer & UI/UX Designer

• Hangzhou, Zhejiang Province, China.

reachtoabdul@gmail.com

86-13735412241

www.aymaraya.github.io

ീത abdullmaraya

o ay.devs

🤈 abdull_maraya

abdull_maraya

Self-motivated Developer & UI/UX Designer with experience working on multiple projects. Passionate and hard-working with a penchant for meeting deadlines. Background includes Software and Hardware development work focused on experiencing real-world experiments and building Tech career. Research-driven and highly organized bringing articulate communication skills and strong attention to detail.

Work Experience

UI/UX Designer

Midland Digital Solutions, Lagos. (June 2020 - Oct 2020)

Head of Software Unit & UI/UX Designer

Mudatex, Kano. (June 2019 - Oct 2019)

Front-end Developer

Steamledge limited, Kano. (Sept 2018 - June 2019)

System Administrator

UBACC, Kano. (Feb 2016 - April 2017)

Education

Bachelors in Robotics Engineering

ZUST, China. (Sept 2020 - Present)

Int'l Diploma in IT & Computing

JSIIT, Nigeria. (July 2017 - Aug 2018)

Skills

UI Design
Web Development
Mobile App Development
Hard-ware Development
Data Collection & Analysis

Tools

Figma
Adobe Photoshop
Basic IDEs
Wondershare Filmora
MS Office / GSuite
Arduino & other dev boards

Programming

HTMI, CSS & Javascript ReactJS & ReactNative Basic C, Java & Python